{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"2583/8",
			"answer":"2583/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8885/4",
			"answer":"8885/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2796/6",
			"answer":"2796/6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3117/6",
			"answer":"3117/6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1809/9",
			"answer":"1809/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"210/0.02",
			"answer":"210/0.02",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"110/5",
			"answer":"110/5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7.65/0.05",
			"answer":"7.65/0.05",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.462/6",
			"answer":"0.462/6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"74.6/0.2",
			"answer":"74.6/0.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"95.5/5",
			"answer":"95.5/5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3.78/0.7",
			"answer":"3.78/0.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"19.2/8",
			"answer":"19.2/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"90/0.9",
			"answer":"90/0.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1.71/0.0009",
			"answer":"1.71/0.0009",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"44.5/0.05",
			"answer":"44.5/0.05",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.132/0.4",
			"answer":"0.132/0.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"680/0.08",
			"answer":"680/0.08",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.4/0.06",
			"answer":"2.4/0.06",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"63.3/0.003",
			"answer":"63.3/0.003",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	
	]
}